https://starshot.com/terms-and-conditions/

Instagram
STARSHOT VENTURES INC. AND STARSHOT VENTURES LLC. (“STARSHOT”) WEBSITEBy accessing this website you agree to be bound by these Terms & Conditions (“Terms). If you do not agree you should not access or view this website.1. ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS FOR WEBSITE USEStarshot Ventures Inc. and Starshot Ventures LLC. (collectively here “STARSHOT”) provide this website subject to the terms and conditions stated here to you (“YOU”) and YOU accept them by using the site for YOUR personal use or that of YOUR employer. If YOU do not agree to these terms please do not use this site.2. YOUR OBLIGATIONS AND CONDUCTAs user of this site it is YOUR responsibility to: (a) provide accurate, current, and complete information if prompted (b) maintain the security of your username or password; and (c) accept all risks and responsibility of unauthorized access to information and any registration data.CONTENT refers to any digital representation of information of any kind YOU may contribute to this website. STARSHOT is not responsible for any content YOU place on our site.YOU are entirely responsible for the content and nature of anything YOU upload, post or otherwise transmit via the Website.YOU agree not to upload, post or otherwise transmit via the Website that will be illegal, offensive, harassing or otherwise inappropriate.STARSHOT reserves the right to edit or remove content that violates these Terms or that contains third-party commercial advertisements. STARSHOT does not routinely monitor Content, but STARSHOT reserve the right to monitor, restrict access to, edit or remove any Content that is available via the Website.STARSHOT is not responsible for the availability of externally linked sites or resources on this site , and does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products, or other materials on or available from such sites or resources.YOU will not use the site to engage in any fraudulent or illegal activity as deemed in any jurisdiction on YOUR behalf or under any assumed identity.  Anything YOU do upload, unless stated in STASHOT’s Privacy Statement, STARSHOT does not claim ownership of and is deemed to be provided on a non-confidential basis. STARSHOT is free to use or disseminate such Content on an unrestricted basis for any purpose, and YOU grant STARSHOT and all other users of the Website an irrevocable, worldwide, royalty-free, nonexclusive license to use, reproduce, modify, distribute, transmit, display, perform, adapt, resell and publish such Content (including in digital form). YOU represent and warrant that you have proper authorization for the worldwide transfer and processing among STARSHOT, its affiliates, and third-party providers of any information that YOU may provide on the Website.3. INDEMNITYYOU agree to indemnify and hold STARSHOT and its subsidiaries, affiliates, shareholders, officers, directors, agents, licensors, suppliers, alliance members, other partners, employees and representatives harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of YOUR Content, YOUR use of or connection to the Website (including any use by YOU on behalf of YOUR employer), YOUR violation of the Terms, or YOUR violation of any rights of another.4. INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS4.1 Except as expressly authorized by STARSHOT or by Content providers, YOU agree not to use in any way, in whole or in part, by any means the site CONTENT. YOU must not copy, use, modify, decompile, or reverse engineer any software STARSHOT discloses to YOU, and You must not remove or modify any copyright or trademark notice, or other notice of ownership. “STARSHOT  Trademarks” means all names, marks, brands, logos, designs, trade dress, slogans and other designations STARSHOT uses in connection with its products and services. YOU may not remove or alter any STARSHOT Trademarks, or co-brand YOUR own products or material with STARSHOT Trademarks, without STARSHOT prior written consent.4.2 YOU assume all risks for any damage to your computer system or information contained therein due to any technical connection to the STARSHOT site or content posted there, including damages resulting from computer viruses.5. STARSHOT PRIVACY POLICYYou consent to the collection, processing and storage by STARSHOT of YOUR personal information in accordance with the terms of STARSHOT Privacy Policy, which is available upon your request. YOU agree to comply with all applicable laws and regulations, and the terms of the STARSHOT Privacy Policy, with respect to any access, use and/or submission by YOU of any personal information in connection with this Website.6. GENERAL TERMSThese Terms and Conditions are governed by and to be interpreted in accordance with the laws of the Province of Ontario, Canada and the State of Illinois, United States of America, in the event of any dispute arising in relation to these Terms and Conditions or any dispute arising in relation to the Website whether in contract or tort or otherwise the Ontario courts will have exclusive jurisdiction over such dispute, unless mandatory applicable law requires otherwise. Rights and obligations under the Terms which by their nature should survive will remain in full effect after termination or expiration of the Terms.TORONTO + CHICAGO1 . 866 . 782 . 7836TORONTO3555 Lake Shore Blvd. W Toronto, Ontario M8W 1P4CHICAGO117 N. Jefferson Street, # 202 Chicago, Illinois 60661INDUSTRIESEnterprise SoftwareCloud SolutionsDevice & HardwareAccounting & FinServStorage and Big DataTelecomPublic Sector & SecurityGreen TechnologyHealthcare TechnologyDigital AdvertisingStay connected
Facebook
Linkedin
Instagram
Twitter
Copyright © 1999-2020 Starshot Ventures Inc.Terms and Conditions     |     Privacy Policy
